[music]
Hi everyone, we are from Hubine. Today
we'll be presenting about health
insurance from Credential Malaysia. Bye.
>> A few moments later.
>> Hello. Yeah.
>> Why did you leave office early
yesterday? I went to insurance center to
renew my insurance.
>> Oh, insurance. Whats insurance did you
take? Is it really important?
>> Yes, of course. If anything happen, you
can make a claim. I choose potential
insurance for my insurance.
>> Wow, sounds good. [music] But I think I
will take it eventually.
>> Yes, you should. It's better for you to
be prepared now.
Okay, but for now, I think I can take
care of myself.
>> [music]
>> You are my everything.
[music]
[singing]
Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
After
doing college, are you okay? [music]
You look so pale. Did you skip lunch
again or do you stress because of the
report? Yeah, I think it's bad. My
workload has been insert and now my body
is telling me [music] something is
wrong. M
We should go to the hospital
immediately. I will come with you.
>> Oh, okay. Maybe I like I don't want it
to get worse. Let's go. [music]
[music]
>> Uh we stand another shot.
>> Yes, I am.
>> Okay. Based on your result and your
blood pressure, you are experiencing a
health stress related illness. So, uh we
might have to run some test and possibly
admit you for an observation.
>> That sounds so serious. How long I need
to stay?
>> Uh it depends on your results, but you
might have to stay at least one night,
but a private hospital might cost a lot.
[music]
>> Expensive? How much are we talking
about?
>> Okay, for a private hospital, it might
cost a few thousand ringit. But this is
why having a medical very
insurance can really make a difference
when emergency happen.
Can I help you?
>> Yes, basically I am sick and the doctor
told me to take out medical insurance.
>> What does blue help cover?
>> Okay, basically health insurance is
important because in an accident can
happen anytime. Imagine placing a
heartfield hospital without support. It
can be such a right. The policy we are
presenting today is [music] real health
by provincial manager with double
hospitalation surgery is treatment and
pre and post hospital care [music] even
minor procedure or surgery are included.
This ensure patient can focus on
recovery rather than worrying about
money.
>> Wow, I didn't realize insurance could
help so much in real situation.
Exactly. That's why getting coverage
early are important
[music]
policy we are present health it provide
financial protected against unexpected
[music]
medical expenses. So the scope uh which
is host hospitalities and surgery
[music] expenses room uh incentive uh
unit which is [music] ICU pre hospital
and post hospital treatment this surgery
[bell]
included yes uh mega major products
[music] are covered so patient don't pay
out of pocket for the necessary [music]
treatment which is benefit include like
hy
Asian [music]
family hospital
[music]
>> during medical emergency.
>> This is very helpful.
Finally, exclusion include illness
during the waiting period, [music]
cosmetic or plastic surgery, self in
medical necessary treatment is important
for [music] understanding to avoid
unexpected cost injuries and have
identified different issues reduces
financial stress individual focus
[music] on recovery from perspective.
The insurance industry offers
opportunities with agents, consultants
and financial planners [music] for
minimizing medical costs. Demand for
insurance in Malaysia is growing
providing health protection and
financial security.
[music]
>> [music]